We have breaking news!
さあ 事件発生です
Robbers attacked an armored truck
先ほどシュテルンメダユウ地区
ウエストシルバーで現金輸送車が襲われ
in West Silver, in the Stern Medaille area,
and made off with three million Stern dollars.
300万シュテルンドルが
強奪されました
ああ
Oh no! The police car!
なんと！ パトカーが
Will they let them make off with the cash?
このまま逃げ切られてしまうのか？
We still haven't spotted any Heroes.
未だヒーローの姿は確認できません
As all of you know, we bring coverage
なお この番組はみなさんご存知
超能力を持つヒーローたちが
of super-powered Heroes taking on crimes
犯罪や災害など
実際の事件現場で活躍する模様を
and natural disasters, straight to your living room!
生放送でお茶の間にお届け！
The rescue entertainment program
活躍の内容に見合ったポイントを加算し
that rates Heroes by their actions
キング オブ ヒーローを
決めてしまおうという
to pick the King of Heroes! This is HERO TV LIVE!
エンターテイメント・レスキュー番組
ヒーローＴＶライブ
gokigen yo doukashitan darou?
How are you? Is something wrong?
ごきげんよう　どうかしたんだろ？
kao wo mireba isshun de wakaru yo
I can tell just by looking at you.
顏を見れば一瞬でわかるよ
senrigan senrigan? messou nai desu
Am I psychic? Of course not.
千里眼千里眼？
めっそうないです
taikutsu GIRL megumaretai no kai
Bored girl, do you want to find happiness?
退屈ガ一ル　恵まれたいのかい
hantei wa shingi no renzoku de
Let's think it through and decide.
判定は審議の連続で
VENUS SUSTAIN
Venus Sustain.
ヴィ一ナスサステイン
odoru machinami
The city dances.
踊る街並み
PERFECTLY EUPHORIA
Perfectly, Euphoria!
Perfectly Euphoria！
nandemo nai youna kotoba de naitari suru shi
I end up crying over the smallest things.
何でもないような
言葉で泣いたりするし
hora bokutachi nante
Come on, our
ほら　僕達なんて
zentei no nai
temporary passion
juubun tekido ni
lives are
十分適度に
zentei no nai
a temporary passion
DRAMATIC sa
reasonably dramatic.
ドラマチックさ
saikou no wa
the best passion
karuku SUPER STAR
We're almost like super stars!
軽くス一パ一スタ一
ORION wo nazoru konna fukai yoru
Looking up at Orion late at night.
オリオンをなぞる こんな深い夜
tsunagaretai hanasaretai
I want to connect. I want to be free.
つながりたい　離されたい
tsumari hanshinhangi acchi kocchi
Basically, I'm not sure and can't decide.
つまり半信半疑あっちこっち
shin mirai wo negau kuuzenzetsugo no
I pray for a new future. The greatest one yet.
新未来を願う　空前絶後の
kotoba ga moshi, moshi tsumugeru nara jikan ga tomaru yo
If I could spin words, time would stop.
言葉がもし もし紡げるなら
時間が止まるよ
koko de owaru hazu ga nai no ni
"There's no way it can end here."
｢ココデオワルハズガナイノニ｣
あーっと 来たあ！
And here comes one now!
It's Fire Emblem, the Bourgeois Open Flame Broil!
ブルジョア直火焼き
ファイヤーエンブレムだ
今日も華麗に
犯人逮捕となるのでしょうか？
Will he be able to make a grand arrest today?!
カメラ！ もっと寄って
Get the camera up close!
Got it!
了解
He's caught up with the suspect...
さあ！ 見事なハンドルさばきで
犯人を追いつめた
with his skillful driving!
もう 来やがった
They've already come.
チッ！
Eat this!
オラーッ！
ソレーッ！
エッ！
アッ！
ウッ！
Yes! Is he going to use his Fireball?!
もう出るのか？　ファイアーボール
A merciless attack!
容赦ない攻撃
Do something!
なんとか なんねえのか？
うるせえ！
Shut up!
犯人たちは どうすることもできない
The suspects are helpless!
And there's another one!
あーっと 来ました！
It's Rock Bison, the Bull Tank of the West Coast!
西海岸の猛牛戦車 ロックバイソン
今シーズンはいい所がなかった
ロックバイソン
Things haven't been good for Rock Bison this season!
久しぶりに
活躍を見ることができそうです
It looks like we'll be able to see him in action
for the first time in quite a while!
フンッ！ エッ え？
Huh?
おっおい！ こらっ！
H-Hey, stop!
It seems that Rock Bison cannot pull out his horns!
ロックバイソン　角が抜けないようだ
Oh no... A taxi was hijacked!
なあーっ　タクシーが奪われた
うーん　もう
Oh shucks!
Coming down from the sky is Dragon Kid,
空から降ってきたのは
稲妻カンフーマスター
ドラゴンキッド
the Lightning Bolt Kung Fu Master!
Wow!
なんと　高圧電流が集まった
腕の必殺ブローで
She charged up her arms and released her special attack!
Two suspects are under arrest!
２人逮捕だ
まさにこの瞬間
It's that moment we love!
And as usual, Origami Cyclone
いつものように折紙サイクロンが
見切れております
can be seen in the background.
さあ これで事件は…
This incident is now...
Huh?
おっ あーっと
Oh no! One of the robbers is still on the run!
強盗犯がまだ１人逃走を続けていた
わああ
早く出せ！
Hurry up and move out!
これは大変なことになりました
This is terrible! According to the information we just received,
ただ今入った情報によりますと
強盗犯がモノレールを
ジャックした模様です
the robber has hijacked a monorail.
What's going on?
Go slower!
What should we do?
どうします？
It's best not to interfere with...
ここは下手に手出ししない方が…
Are you trying to ruin my program?
私の番組　台無しにする気？
だけど市民の安全が…
But the safety of the citizens...
あっ！ あれ
Look! There...
Wow.
わーお
おーっと 大丈夫か？
Are you sure he's okay?!
Wild Tiger, the Crusher for Justice,
こんな大変な場面で
正義の壊し屋ワイルドタイガーが登場
has shown up in this terrible situation.
Now cut to commercial!
じゃあ ＣＭ行って
タイガー　聞こえる？
Tiger, can you hear me?
Get started once the 30-second commercial is over!
30秒後 ＣＭ明けてからゴーよ
はあ？ ＣＭ？
Huh? Commercial?
こんな時にＣＭ待ちなんか
してられっかよ
I can't wait for a commercial at a time like this!
ちょっと　言うこと聞きなさい
Hey! Listen to me!
Things will be more exciting my way!
その方が盛り上がるでしょ？
I don't care about that.
知らねえよ
俺達ヒーローは
We Heroes only care about keeping the peace!
平和を守れりゃ
それでいいんだよ
Wild roar!
ワイルドに吠えるぜ！
また… あいつ…
He's doing it again.
続けて！
Continue!
Oh, okay.
ああ　はい
なーんと ここでワイルドタイガー
ハンドレッドパワー発動
What's this?!
Wild Tiger is activating his Hundred Power!
これにより身体能力は通常時の…
This makes his physical abilities...
速く進め！
Go faster!
無理です
I can't.
おりゃー
...a hundred times more powerful!
100倍に
早く止めろ　衝突する
Stop right now!
I can't!
Stop!
おりゃー
おとなしく観念…
Give up!
あれっ？
Huh?
You idiot! Below you!
バカ！ 下よ下！
だぁ！ いつの間に
When did he get there?
The robber has gotten on an airship!
強盗犯は飛行船に移動
チェッ！
はあ？
And here comes Sky High, the Windmaster!
ここで来たのは風使いのスカイハイ
今シーズン圧倒的な活躍を見せる
ミスターヒーローがいよいよ登場！
Mr. Hero,
the star player this season, is on the scene!
Go!
That bastard!
あの野郎
おいしい所で出てきやがって
Showing up during the best part!
無駄な抵抗はやめろ
Don't try to stop me.
Don't try to stop me!
無駄な抵抗はやめろ
エッ？
言うこと かぶってんじゃねえ
Don't copy me!
はあ？
へぇー どわーっ！
とりゃ！
あー！
犯人の打った弾が大爆発
Oh no! The suspect's missile has exploded!
はーあっ！
He's controlling the wind to save people first!
風を操り人命救助を最優先
Just what we'd expect from Sky High!
さすがスカイハイ
まさにキング オブ ヒーロー
He truly is the King of Heroes!
スカイハイ がんばれ！
Yay, Sky High!
He's so cool!
Uh-oh! The airship just crashed into a building!
なんと！
飛行船はビルに激突か？
助けてくれー　スカイハイ
Save me! Sky High!
来たぞ
Wild Tiger...
at your service!
ワイルドタイガーだ
行くぞ
Let's go!
いや　スカイハイを待つよ
No, I'll wait for Sky High.
Shut up! You'll be fine with me!
うるせえ！　俺で平気だよ
どぉ
んっ！　このままだと客船にぶつかる
It's going to crash into a passenger boat!
だあっ　ヤベッ！
Oh boy!
Save us!
Wha—?
エエッ？
Quit wasting your time.
なーに ちんたらやってるの？
Huh?
This is the moment you fans have been waiting for!
ファンの皆様　お待たせしました
Blue Rose, the super star of the Hero world,
ヒーロー界のスーパーアイドル
ブルーローズが
has saved the passenger ship with her Freezing Liquid Gun!
フリージングリキッドガンで
客船を救出
Ｂカメ ローアングルから回り込んで
Camera B! Get a shot from below!
My ice is a little cold,
私の氷はちょっぴりコールド
but your crime has been put completely on hold!
あなたの悪事を完全ホールド
She's done it!
決まったあ
Do you just want to rack up numbers?!
そんなに数字が欲しいのかよ
I caught the suspect here, you know!
あ こっちー
犯人捕まえたんですけど
はあ
Switcher!
スイッチャー
あっ
You...
お前
てめえが邪魔するからだ
It's your fault for interfering!
あー 何してくれたんだ
What are you doing?
無事です
He's all right! Wild Tiger was shot, but he's all right!
打たれたワイルドタイガーは
無事のようです
ん？
Hm? Oh.
うわあ
Hey!
ちょっと　こっち来ないでよ
Don't come this way!
あっ
もう
I can't take this anymore!
It's her explosive Cutie Escape!
何と！　炸裂
キューティーエスケープ
She's just running away.
逃げてるだけだろ
危なっ！
What an amazing jump!
すごいジャンプだ
Bastard!
He's out of time!
時間切れ
ワイルドタイガーの能力は
５分間しか持たない
Wild Tiger's power only lasts for five minutes!
あっ やっべー
Oh no!
普通の人間に戻ってしまったタイガー
Tiger has changed back into a normal person!
このままでは危なーい
He's in danger!
ああ？
あれ？
Huh?
Who are you?
誰だ？ お前
Don't try to push yourself.
無理は いけませんよ
だあー
ぬあっ
It's... Uh, who is he?
だあー
えっ 誰？
Oh...
ああ？
うわー
The mystery man has arrested the suspect!
あーっと 謎の男が犯人を逮捕
うーっ
あっ
ふっ
Is this the birth of a new star?
これは新しいスターの誕生でしょうか？
This season ends with a mysterious Hero!
謎のヒーローが今シーズンを
締めくくりました
He's so cool!
Amazing!
はああ
Cut to a commercial!
いったんＣＭ！
Life is freedom
思い通り生きるわ
My shiny days
ひかる星よりも　Yes！ 眩しく
おい お前 所属どこだ？
Hey.
What's your affiliation?
Affiliation?
所属？
フリーのくせに首突っ込んだのか？
You're a free agent,
yet you decided to stick your neck into this?
何考えてんだ
What's the big idea?
What does it matter? We made an arrest.
いいじゃないですか
逮捕できたんですから
だいたいお前な
Anyway, a Hero shouldn't remove
ヒーローが人前で
仮面外したりなんかすんな
his mask in front of other people.
It's unheard of!
ありえねえぞ
Huh?
は？
Heroes never reveal their identities.
ヒーローってのはな
正体を明かさないのが
ヒーローなんであって…
古いな
How old-fashioned.
え？
Huh?
You've fallen behind the times, old man.
あなたは もう時代遅れなんですよ
おじさん
What?
なに？
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
それでは皆様
大変お待たせいたしました
ヒーローＴＶ
今シーズンの結果発表です
We're about to announce the results of this season's HERO TV.
反省してんのか？　虎徹
Do you realize what you've done, Kotetsu?
Why did you have to bend the rail?
どうしてレールを
ひん曲げなきゃいけなかった？
And you didn't have to break the car windows, did you?
車両の窓だって割らずに済んだよな？
Well...
まあ
Then why did you break them?
じゃ どうして壊した？
Do you know how much they cost?
あれ いくらかかるか知ってる？
If I worried about that, I wouldn't be able to keep the peace.
そんなの気にしてたら
平和なんて守れないっすよ
If you don't worry about that, I can't protect you!
それを気にしてくれなきゃ
俺がお前を守れないんだよ
Sorry for always causing you trouble.
ええ いつもすんません
You do know who made you a Hero, don't you?
誰のおかげでヒーローできてるか
わかってるよな？
スポンサー様です
Our sponsors, sir!
Good. Now go to the award ceremony!
よしっ　行って来い！　表彰式へ
Okay!
はい
Fire Emblem!
ファイヤーエンブレム
ロックバイソン
Rock Bison!
ドラゴンキッド
Dragon Kid!
折紙サイクロン
Origami Cyclone!
スカイハイ
Sky High!
ブルーローズ
Blue Rose!
Wild Tiger!
ワイルドタイガー
Who's going to shine as the victor?
さあ 栄冠に輝くのは誰だ？
遅いぞ
You're late.
ＭＶＰの発表は？
When's the MVP announcement?
今から
Right now.
セーフ
Made it in time.
絶対お前じゃないから
It's definitely not you.
うっさい
Shut up.
Thank you for waiting! We are going to announce our MVP!
お待たせいたしました
いよいよＭＶＰの発表です
With 12,730 points... the King of Heroes is Sky High!
獲得ポイント　12730
キング オブ ヒーロー
スカイハイ
Congratulations.
おめでとうございます
皆さんの応援のおかげです
I couldn't have done this without everyone's help.
Thanks, and thanks again!
ありがとう
そして ありがとう
続きましてアポロンメディアＣＥＯ兼
ＯＢＣ社長アルバートマーベリックより
Next, a message from Albert Maverick,
the CEO of Apollon Media as well as the president of OBC!
挨拶をさせて頂きます
と その前に皆さんに
紹介したい人物が…
Before that, there is someone I'd like to introduce.
Please come in.
入りたまえ
Barnaby Brooks Jr. here has been officially approved
彼はこの度
司法局の正式な認可を受けた
by the Justice Bureau.
バーナビー・ブルックスJr.
He is the new Hero who will be keeping the peace in Stern Bild.
シュテルンビルドの平和を
守ることになったニューヒーローです
フッ
"Heh," my ass!
フッ　じゃねえよ
まあまあ
Now, now...
彼は能力を発動することにより
When he activates his power, he can make his physical abilities
身体能力を通常時の100倍に
高めることができるのです
a hundred times more powerful.
えっ？
Huh?
発動時間は５分だけと
He can only activate it for five minutes at a time,
あるヒーローとまったく同じ能力ですが
何と言っても彼はまだ若い
and shares the exact same power as another Hero...
But he is young!
間違ってもお姫様抱っこされるような
ヒーローにはならないように
Try not to become a Hero who needs rescuing.
えー ＮＥＸＴという特殊能力者が
この世に突然変異で現れてから45年…
Individuals with super powers, known as NEXT,
suddenly appeared in this world
45 years ago due to a mutation.
We still don't know what triggers these powers.
Hey!
おいっ
帰るわ
I'm leaving.
しかし町の平和が守られているのは
彼らＮＥＸＴ
What we do know is that peace
has been upheld in this city because these NEXT—
つまり能力者がヒーローとして
in other words, people with special powers,
働いてくれている
おかげだということです
have worked as Heroes.
Welcome.
いらっしゃい
"A veteran Hero... ten years since making his debut."
デビュー10年を迎えたベテランヒーロー
峠を過ぎた感が あるものの
"Though he is past his prime, he still..."
ふんっ
おおっ
I'd like ten of these, ma'am!
あっ おばちゃん　これ10枚
はいよ
Okay.
えっ
What's up?
おお　どうした？
Hey, aren't you going to come to the celebration?
おい　打ち上げも来ないのかよ
そういうの苦手なんだよ
I don't really care for those things.
You should greet the bigwigs.
お偉いさんたちには
ちゃんと挨拶した方がいいぞ
Then you take care of that for me.
じゃっ 俺の分も頼んだから
Oh, hey!
あっ おい うーん
ひえー
Your butt always feels nice.
いつ触っても いいお尻
Y-You idiot! Get away from me!
離れろ
The way you showed up in the background was splendid.
今日の見切れ方最高でした
次回もお願いしますよ
I want you to do it again next time.
バッチリ企業名アピールするでござる
I'll try to bring the spotlight on the company name. I mean, I will.
あっいや　しますから
President, my catch phrase is embarrassing.
社長 あの決めゼリフ
恥ずかしいんで変えちゃダメですか？
Can I change it?
あの上からな感じが人気なんだよ
That domineering attitude is what makes you so popular.
ふっ わかってないね
You just don't get it, do you?
Thanks, and thanks again!
感謝します　そして感謝します
Mr. Maverick!
マーベリックさん
いやあ
Making you the producer of this program was the right choice.
この番組のプロデューサ−を君に替えて
正解だったよ
I never expected you to pull in these ratings.
ここまで視聴率が取れるなんてね
このアニエスジュベールが
もっともっと
I, Agnes Joubert, will make it much more intense!
過激にしますわ
Coming, coming, coming...
はい はい はい
Hello?
はーい
お父さん？
Dad?
おっどうした　楓？
Hey! What is it, Kaede?
明日の発表会 忘れてないよね？
You haven't forgotten about my recital tomorrow, have you?
Of course not!
もちろん
パパ見に行くって約束したろ？
I promised that I'd be there.
Ouch!
ホントに？
Really? You don't have to work?
お父さん お仕事だったりしない？
大丈夫
It's all right!
明日は楓のかわいい姿を
ちゃーんと この目に焼き付けるからね
Tomorrow, I'm going to get a good look at how cute you are!
パパ 必ず行く
I wouldn't miss it!
ああ そうかい
Oh, is that so?
You should tell me that you've taken the phone, Mom!
代わったら代わったって言えよ
かあちゃん
テレビ見てたよ
また賠償金？
I was watching the TV. Do you have to pay for damages again?
ああ あはは
You get reckless when you get worked up. Be careful.
あんた 熱くなると
みさかえ無くなるから
気をつけなさいよ
わかってるよ
I know.
Anyway, if you die,
とにかく あんたが死んだら
“実はお父さんは
ヒーローだったんだよ”なんて
I'm going to have to tell Kaede that her father was a Hero.
楓に言わなきゃならないんだから
ホントに気を付けてよ
I really want you to be careful.
心配しすぎだって
You worry too much.
心配するわよ
I can't help it!
娘と離れてまでやらなきゃいけない
仕事なんて
You have to keep your work a secret from your own daughter.
心配しない方がおかしいでしょ
It would be strange if I didn't worry.
ああ わかってる　わかってるよ
Yeah I know... I know.
What?!
だあっ
Sorry, Kotetsu.
すまねえな　虎徹
おおっ　ベンさん
Ben...
A buyout?
合弁？
大手資本の加入だ
Big money is involved.
まあ うちも資金繰りに困ってたし
We were struggling with funds, so we found a good buyer.
いい買い手が見つかったってとこだ
Here.
ほれっ
んっ？ 誰っすか？
こいつ
Huh?
Who is this guy?
お前の新しい上司だよ
Your new boss.
あっ？
Huh?
Go say hello right now.
今から そこいって挨拶してこい
ちょっと待ってくださいよ
状況がさっぱり…
Wait a second. I don't understand what's going on.
Starting next season,
来季からヒーローを
７つの大手企業で独占
only the seven major companies are going to have Heroes.
統括していくって話だ
で わが社がその最後の会社だったわけ
And our company was the last one to go.
要は無くなるって そういうこと？
In other words, we're going to disappear?
You don't need to know this.
お前はわからんでもいい
Did the other Heroes know about this?
他のヒーローは知ってたんすか？
Was I the only one who didn't know?
俺だけかよ
Sorry.
すまん
What are you going to do?
で ベンさんはどうすんだよ？
Don't worry about me.
俺のことは心配すんな
I'm going to take it easy on unemployment insurance
まあ失業保険でのんびりしながら
次の仕事でも探すよ
and look for another job.
I can't go by myself.
俺だけ行くなんてできない
It's all right.
いいんだ
だけど…
But...
いいんだよ
It's all right.
Not being able to see you fight as a Hero is much worse.
お前のヒーロー姿が見られない方が辛い
俺は これからもずっと
I'll always be a fan of Wild Tiger. Got it?
ワイルドタイガーのファンだからな
ん？
フッ
ああー
んん？ ここか
This is the place, eh?
ん？
うーん
There we go!
よっとお！
どぁーっと
あっ
はいよ
Here.
ありがとう
Thank you.
You dropped those.
これ
今落ちたよ
Oh. Those are...
あっ いや これは…
Say, mister... Are you...
ねえ おじちゃん もしかして
Darn, you figured it out?
まいったな バレちゃったか
You like Tiger, don't you?!
おじちゃん タイガーが好きなんだね
Huh?
In that case, I'll give you this.
じゃこれ　あげるよ
You don't have to do that. This is your treasure, isn't it?
いいよ いいよ
君の大事なものなんだろ
僕 スカイハイのファンだから
いらないの　あげる
I'm a Sky High fan, so I don't need it. You can have it.
Is that so?
ああ そう？
I see. I'm unwanted...
そう いらないの
君がワイルドタイガー？
Are you Wild Tiger?
You got Tiger from your name Toratetsu, huh?
ああ “とらてつ”って名前だから
タイガーか
“こてつ”です
It's Kotetsu. Kaburagi Kotetsu.
鏑木虎徹
ふーん
You will be briefed about your suit
じゃあ 開発部で
スーツの説明を受けてもらおうか
at the Development Department.
Well, I hadn't heard that we were doing this today.
いや 今日からって
聞いてないんですが
You can quit if you don't want to.
嫌なら辞めてもらってもいいよ
I'll do it.
やります
Is it the industrial district?
工業地区か
The Steel Hammer Statue?
スティールハンマー像？
Why is it moving?
なーんで動いてんだ
A NEXT might be behind this.
ＮＥＸＴの仕業かも知れません
All right, head out right away.
よし　早速出動して
え？ いやっ でも
スーツないですし
Huh? But I don't have a suit.
I have one for you right here.
それはこちらで用意したから
はぁ
I want you to make use of your new suit.
これからは新しいスーツで
活動してもらう
“んなことできるか！　”です
I can't do that... sir.
Do you have a problem with it?
何か不満でも
I have no intention of wearing any suit other than my own.
俺は自分のスーツ以外
着るつもりは ありません
Don't worry.
安心して　性能は君が着てたものより
はるかに上だ
The specs on this one are far better than the one you wore.
そういう問題じゃないんです
That's not the issue here. I need to wear that suit to be a Hero!
俺にとってヒーローってのは
あのスーツじゃなきゃ ダメなんです
It's what I aspire to become...
あの姿は俺のあこがれの…
いいから早く行きたまえ
Just get going already.
Actually, this is nice.
意外にいいな　これ
It's him.
あいつか
All right...
よーし
One important thing.
大事なことが１つ
君には あるヒーローと
組んでもらうから
I'm going to pair you up with another Hero.
は？
Huh?
The first team in the Hero world...
ヒーロー界初のコンビ結成
それが我がアポロンメディアの売りだ
That's what Apollon Media is going to sell.
I hadn't heard about that.
そんなん聞いてないんですが
If you don't like it, you can quit.
嫌なら辞めてもらってもいいよ
What's this about a team?! Who am I pairing up with?
何だよ　コンビって
誰と組めっていうん… ん？
だああ
That hurts... I guess I can't do this by myself.
痛ってえ
やっぱ１人じゃ無理か
エッ　お前？
Huh? You?!
僕が消え 遠い未来で
boku ga kie tooi mirai de kaseki ni nattara
When I die and become a fossil in the far future,
化石になったら
人は僕に何を見るだろう
hito wa boku ni nani wo miru darou?
what will people see me as?
分析して 名を付けて
bunseki shite na wo tsukete kaidoku wo shitemo
They may try to analyze, name, and understand me,
解読をしても
愛した人は僕しか知らない
aishita hito wa boku shika shiranai
but only I will know the person I loved.
ハロ一 生きること
HELLO ikiru koto
Hello, existence.
君の他に 君はできない
kimi no hoka ni kimi wa dekinai
Only you alone can live your life.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
僕らは何を感じられるだろう
bokura wa nani wo kanjirareru darou?
What can we feel from it?
奇跡は宇宙だけじゃないよ
kiseki wa uchuu dake janai yo
The universe isn't the only miracle.
輝き続ける光った星から
kagayaki tsuzukeru hikatta hoshi kara
From the bright star that continues to shine,
輝き続け 光ったあの空から
kagayaki tsuzuke hikatta ano sora kara
from that bright sky that continues to shine.
目を閉じたって 閉じきれないよ
me wo tojitatte tojikirenaiyo
You can try to shut your eyes, but you can't shut out your heart.
あの星さえ 持てなかった心
ano hoshi sae motenakatta kokoro
It's something that even the stars did not possess.
エッ！ マジ？
ロックバイソンなの
Huh? Really? With you, Rock Bison?
はあ？
いや はあ？ じゃなくて
Huh?
What do you mean, "Huh"?
お前が俺の…
You're my—
行きますよ　おじさん
Let's go, old man!
お前かあ
You?!
どうも　TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
ヒーロー虎徹です
Hello! I'm Kotetsu, the bearded member of "Tiger & Bunny"!
おっと 石像が暴れだしてるぞ
Whoa! A statue is going wild! Is a NEXT behind this?
犯人はＮＥＸＴか？
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
ア グッド ビギニング メイク…
Next time on TIGER & BUNNY:
読めねえよ
I don't know what this says!